League of Women Voters mss., 1913-2014 LMC 2371
Lilly Library
League of Women Voters mss.
1913-2014
Lilly Library
League of Women Voters of Bloomington-Monroe County
LMC 2371
6500 Items
The League of Women Voters mss., 1913-2014, consist of the records of the League of Women Voters (LWV) of Monroe County, Indiana.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Biographical Note
The LWV is an American civic organization that was formed to help women take a larger role in public affairs as they won the right to vote. It was founded in 1920 by Carrie Chapman Catt during the last meeting of the National American Woman Suffrage Association, approximately six months before the Nineteenth Amendment to the United States Constitution gave women the right to vote. LWV operates at the local, state, and national level, with over 1,000 local and 50 state leagues, including Indiana. Its mission statement reads: "The LWV is a nonpartisan political organization encouraging informed and active participation in government. It influences public policy through education and advocacy."
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into the following series: I. Bound Items, II. Administrative Files, III. Marge and Faber Files, IV. 2016 Additions, and V. 2018 Additions.
Scope and Content Note
The collection includes annual reports, correspondence, financial statements, minutes of meetings, newsletters, photographs, LWV publications (e.g., "Here is Your Local Government" and "A Guide to Bloomington Monroe County") brochures, flyers, and news clippings. Also included is a composition book, 1913-1919, which contains the minutes of the first meetings organizing the "Bloomington Branch of the Women's Franchise League."
Acquisition Information
Acquired: 2001, 2007 - 2008
Women--Suffrage--Indiana.; Bloomington (Ind.)--Politics and government.; Monroe County (Ind.)--Politics and government.; Bloomington (Ind.)--Biography.; Monroe County (Ind.)--Biography.; Indiana--Politics and government; Women; League of Women Voters of Bloomington, Indiana; League of Women Voters of Bloomington-Monroe County.; Woman's Franchise League of Indiana. Bloomington Branch.
- Bound Items
  - Ledger. "Woman's Franchise League, Bloomington. Ind." Lists members and dues paid., 1914-1926
  - Scrapbook. "Bloomington League of W. Voters" Contains: lists of officers and members, financial statements, letters from Senators Sherman Minton and Frederick Van Nuys, news clippings, publications., 1937-1939
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings, by-laws, list of members, publications., 1938-1939
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings, letters, list of members, financial statements, publications, Report of Organization., 1939
  - Scrapbook. Contains: tentative program for open meetings and study groups, by-laws, news clippings, letters, list of officers and members, publications., 1939-1941
  - Secretary's Book. Minutes of meetings, news clippings., 1940, Apr. 25-1950, May 2
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings, letters, list of officers, report of meetings, programs, progress reports, financial statements, publications., 1941-1942
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings, letters, list of officers, reports of plans, organization and activities, publications., 1943-1944
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings, letters, publications., 1944, June-1945, June.
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings, letters, publications., 1945, June-1946, June.
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings and flyers., 1946, June-1947, June.
  - Scrapbook. Contains: Request for Action letter, news clippings., 1947, June-1948, June.
  - Secretary's Book. Minutes of meetings., 1950, May 26-1957, Apr. 1
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings., 1950
- Administrative Files
  - Composition Book. Minutes. Begins "The Bloomington Branch of the Womans Franchise League was organized May 1913." Ends with minutes of the May 1, 1919 meeting taken by Secretary Anna B. Collins. Last page has "dues" for 1916., 1913, May-1919, May 1. (Box 1)
  - Reports of League activities and organization, budget, publications, instructions for congressional interviews, 1938-1940 (Box 1)
  - Loose items removed from Scrapbook: minutes of meetings, news clippings, treasurer's reports, 1940, Apr. 25-1950, May 2 (Box 1)
  - Indiana League of Women Voters Fourth Biennial Council Meeting, Kokomo, IN. Contains: programs, publications, news clippings, headquarters report, 1941, May 14 and 15. (Box 1)
  - Financial records, 1941-1949 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, list of members, reports, publications, newsletter, 1941 (Box 1)
  - War Service Records. Minutes, letters, War Service Bulletins, 1942, Jan-1943, May. (Box 1)
    General
    (2 folders)
  - Correspondence, flyers, publications, reports, "The Equal Rights Amendment and Why it is Opposed!!!", newsletters, news clippings, 1942 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, flyers, publications, reports, newsletters, news clippings, 1943 (Box 1)
  - Loose items removed from Scrapbook: drawings, news clippings, 1944, June-1945, June. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, list of members, pamphlet, 1944-1945 (Box 1)
  - Loose items removed from Scrapbook: newsletter, news bulletins, League High-Lights, 1945, June-1946, June. (Box 1)
  - History of The Indiana League of Women Voters During World War II, 1941-1945, by Caroline M. Goodwin; related printed items, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Loose items removed from Scrapbook: news bulletin and League High-Lights, 1946, June-1947, June. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, publications, bulletins, lists of members, League High-Lights. Also includes: "City of Bloomington Certificate of Award presented to the League of Women Voters of Bloomington, for patriotic service to the city and community for successfully organizing and conducting a Rat Control Program for the City of Bloomington, Given under my hand and seal in the City of Bloomington, Indiana, this 6 day of December, 1949.", 1946-1949 (Box 1)
  - Highlights. Includes lists of past presidents; history of study and action on local program, 1946-1955; copies of Highlights brochure, 1974-1989; various other brochures, 1946-1989 (Box 1)
  - Loose items removed from Scrapbook: League High-Lights, 1947, June-1948 June. (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook. League High-Lights, news clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1949-1950, 1950-1951; proposed local programs; publications, treasurer's report, 1953, 1949-1953 (Box 1)
  - Unit System. Mostly printed materials concerning group discussions, how to run unit meetings, etc., 1949-1974 (Box 1)
  - Loose items removed from 1950 Scrapbook: news clippings, 1950-1951 (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook. Contains: news clippings, letters, voters service report, questionnaires for congressional candidates, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
  - List of members, annual report, budget, correspondence, by-laws, League Highlights, publications, clippings, 1954-1959 (Box 1)
    (6 folders)
  - Distinguished Service Award from the U.S. Junior Chamber of Commerce for 1960; publication "Forty Years of a Great Idea" (Box 2)
  - Reports., 1961 (Box 2)
  - Proclamation - League of Women Voters Week 1962 signed by the mayor of Bloomington, Thomas L. Lemon (Box 2)
  - Distinguished Service Award from the U.S. Junior Chamber of Commerce for 1963 (Box 2)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1965 (Box 2)
  - "On the Waterfront---Monroe County, Indiana: A progress report and supplement to the Bloomington League of Women Voters Publications: A study of the Water Supply and Sewage Disposal Systems of Bloomington, Indiana, September 1965", 1966 (Box 2)
  - Newsletters and accompanying materials, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Membership reports, 1967-1986 (Box 2)
  - Newsletters and accompanying materials, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Newsletters and accompanying materials, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Newsletters and accompanying materials, 1970, Jan.-Sept. (Box 2)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1970, Oct.-Dec. (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1970, Jan.-Aug. (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1970, Sept.-Dec. (Box 2)
  - Annual report, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Work calendar and accompanying materials, 1971, Jan.-June. (Box 2)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1971, July-Dec. (Box 2)
  - Clippings, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1972, Jan.-Apr. (Box 3)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1972, May-Dec. (Box 3)
  - "Here Is Your Local Government", 1972 (Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1973, Jan.-Apr. (Box 3)
  - League letter and accompanying materials, 1973, May-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Printed, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1973 (Box 3)
  - MCCSC building utilization studies, 1973-1980 (Box 3)
  - Newsletters and accompanying materials, 1974, Jan.-Apr. (Box 3)
  - Newsletters and accompanying materials, 1974, May-Oct. (Box 3)
  - League letter and accompanying materials, 1974, Nov.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Finance drive letters, 1974-1986 (Box 3)
    (1 folder)
  - League letter and accompanying materials, 1975 (Box 3)
    (3 folders)
  - Clippings, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Community Support Drive (notebook). Contains: list of contributors, flyers, clippings and other related material, 1976 (Box 4)
  - League letters, clippings, and accompanying materials, 1977 (Box 4)
  - Printed, 1978 (Box 4)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Minutes, 1979-1986 (Box 4)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Finance, 1980 (Box 4)
  - A Guide to Bloomington, Monroe County, Indiana, 1980 (Box 4)
  - "Lake Monroe and watershed area study, maps, photographs", 1980 (Box 5)
  - Prime agriculture land preservation study kit, 1980 (Box 5)
  - School finance project, 1980 (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1981 (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1982 (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Finance, 1983 (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Clippings, 1984 (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1985 (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1986 (Box 5)
  - "A Guide to Bloomington, Monroe Co., Indiana", 1986 (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1987, Jan.-May. (Box 5)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1987, June-Dec. (Box 6)
  - Lists of members, 1987-1992 (Box 6)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1988 (Box 6)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Printed, 1989 (Box 6)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Contribution slips, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Finance drive, 1990 (Box 6)
  - "School finance study update", 1990 (Box 6)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Reports and accompanying materials, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Archives project. Project to photocopy the League of Women Voters/Bloomington archives for the Monroe County Public Library. Contains: Project approval request form, news clipping, and some photocopies, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Clippings, 1991 (Box 6)
  - "Building Partnerships" - 44th Biennial Convention, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Member information, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Clippings, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Clippings, 1994 (Box 7)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1995 (Box 7)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1996 (Box 7)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1997 (Box 7)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1998 (Box 7)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 1999 (Box 7)
  - League letters and accompanying materials, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Impact on Issues, 1998-2000 (Box 7)
  - Campaign Finance Reform: Strategies for Success in the Midwest (Box 7)
  - Legislative Update, Feb. 15, 1992. One VHS tape (Box 7)
  - The League of Women Voters Discussion on Reforming the Forest Service, Mar. 21, 1992. Two VHS tapes (Box 7)
  - Keys, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Candidate forums, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Legislative Updates, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Candidate Forums, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1996 (Box 8)
  - election materials, 1996 (Box 8)
  - candidates, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Candidate packet, 1998 (Box 8)
  - election materials, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Forums - clippings, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 1998 (Box 8)
  - election forums, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Candidate forums, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Candidate Forums, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 2002 (Box 8)
  - candidates - lists, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Forums, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Keys to the candidates, 2003 (Box 8)
  - Candidate forums, 2004 (Box 8)
  - Keys to the candidates, 2004 (Box 8)
  - Primary, 2006 (Box 8)
  - Keys, 2006 (Box 8)
  - 75th anniversary celebration of 19th Amendment, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Public Relations, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
  - How to Vote speech (Box 9)
  - Take a friend to vote [bumper stickers] (Box 9)
  - Election talk materials: general info; voting machine instructions (Box 9)
  - LWV speech (Box 9)
  - LWV Media coverage "Guide to getting god media coverage", 1994 (Box 9)
  - "Voters bill of rights" (Box 9)
  - Voting Rules and Instructions, 1994 (Box 9)
  - LWV General Info, 1994 (Box 9)
  - National Voter Registration Act, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Voters Registration, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Voter service portfolio (Box 9)
  - Voter Service - General, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Motor voter, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Moderator scripts (for candidate forums) (Box 9)
  - Voters Registration Board, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Candidate info, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Voters Registration Board, 1997 (Box 9)
  - election materials, 2000 (Box 9)
  - officials list - distribution, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Indiana voters info guide, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Motot Voter Program, 2001 (Box 9)
  - legislative updates, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Forum procedures, 2002 (Box 9)
  - candidate forums response form, 2002 (Box 9)
  - legislative updates, 2002-2003 (Box 9)
  - election materials, 2002 (Box 9)
  - party chair letters, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Fall, Keys to the candidates, 2006 (Box 9)
  - Annual Meeting, 2012-2013 (Box 10)
  - Annual Meeting Booklet, 1978-1983 (Box 10)
    (4 folders)
  - Health Care Committee, 2007-2012 (Box 10)
  - Membership Lists, 2007-2010 (Box 10)
  - Monroe County Government Officials List, 2011-2014 (Box 10)
  - Working Notes, 2007-2012 (Box 10)
    (31 folders)
  - Study - Privatization - Discussion and Consensus Qs, 2011-2012 (Box 10)
    (9 folders)
  - Study - School Funding, 2011-2012 (Box 10)
  - Minutes and Newsletters, 2012-2013 (Box 10)
  - Voter Registration, 2012 (Box 10)
  - LWV Miscellaneous, 1980-2013 (Box 10)
    (18 folders)
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Education Committee, 2010-2013 (Box 10)
  - Member's Handbook, 2008-2009 (Box 10)
  - Positions, Policies, and Bylaws (Box 10)
  - LMV Binders, 2001-2005 (4) (Box 11)
  - Monroe County Government Officials Lists and accompanying materials, 1995-2008 (Box 12)
    (10 folders)
  - "Neal's Landfill" (Box 12)
  - LMV - working file (Box 12)
  - LMV lawsuit (Box 12)
  - "Incinerator" (Box 12)
  - "Expert Panel Workshop" packet (Box 12)
  - Campaign Finance Reform binder (Box 12)
  - National Convention, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Solar energy (Box 13)
  - Voter registration lawsuit, Mar. 1987 (Box 13)
  - League Leters, 1990s (Box 13)
  - Project Safety Plan (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
  - Binder of records and reports (Box 13)
  - Debate questions (Box 14)
  - Von Wettstein (Box 14)
  - Utilities Service Board (Box 14)
  - Voter registration strategy (Box 14)
  - Voter service (Box 14)
  - Voter registration problems (Box 14)
  - Membership (Box 14)
  - Voter service (Box 14)
  - Agriculture study, 1987-1988 (Box 14)
  - Clean air (Box 14)
  - Energy (Box 14)
  - Public statements, letters, etc. (Box 15)
  - NR Reports (Box 15)
  - Legislative Info, Voting (Box 15)
  - NR Misc (Box 15)
  - Agriculture Study LWVUS (Box 15)
  - NR: HNF (Box 15)
  - NR: Earth Day (Box 15)
  - NR: Energy (Box 15)
  - NR: Environment General (Box 15)
  - NR Pesticides (Box 15)
  - Incineration (Box 15)
  - Landfill (Box 15)
  - Fact Sheets, Unit Info, Chronologies (Box 15)
  - Legislation (Box 15)
  - Recycling (Box 15)
  - League Letter, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
  - NR/SW/MCSWD (Box 15)
  - Nuclear Waste (Box 15)
  - MCCSC newsclippings (Box 16)
  - EPA (Box 16)
  - School Board Assembly - nominating committee (Box 16)
  - LMVUS Government (Box 16)
    (8 folders)
  - Finance (Box 16)
  - Jacobson Lawnmower (Box 16)
  - Former Member Letters (Box 16)
  - Guidelines for Phone Calls (Box 16)
  - General Appeal Letters (Box 16)
  - Fall Letter (Box 16)
  - Fundraising Ideas (Box 16)
  - National Wildlife Federation (Box 16)
  - 1975 Taxes (Box 16)
  - Artwork (Box 16)
  - National Voter (Box 16)
  - Officials List (Box 16)
  - Publication Orders: Local (Box 16)
  - Stationery (Box 16)
  - Tips for Fundraising (Box 16)
  - Finance Drive (Box 16)
  - Traveling (Box 16)
  - League Letter, April 1999 (Box 16)
  - League Letter, December 1998 (Box 16)
  - Monroe County, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Newsletters, 1982-1985 (Box 16)
  - League Letter, 1987-1989 (Box 16)
  - Computer disks (2) (Box 17)
  - Slides (Box 17)
  - Audio-cassettes (7) (Box 17)
  - CD (1) (Box 17)
  - Video-cassettes (26) (Box 17)
  - Reel-to-reel (1) (Box 17)
  - Child care (Box 18)
  - Letterhead/envelopes (Box 18)
  - Social service agencies (Box 18)
  - Deborah (Box 18)
  - Aging, Elderly (Box 18)
  - Evergreen General Meeting (Box 18)
  - Basic Human Needs Study, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Juvenile Justice Task Force (Box 18)
  - Zero Tolerance (Box 18)
  - NCLB (Box 18)
  - Poverty (Box 18)
  - Population (Box 18)
  - Welfare Reform (Box 18)
  - Women - ERA (Box 18)
  - League of Women Voters National Immigration Study 2007 (Box 18)
  - Living Wage (Box 18)
  - Health (Box 18)
  - Death Penalty (Box 18)
  - Childwatch (Box 18)
  - General Assistance (Box 18)
  - National Energy Program (Box 19)
  - Lake Lemon Conservacy (Box 19)
  - On Water Quality (Box 19)
  - Water Quality Study (Box 19)
  - Natural Resources (Box 19)
  - LWV Positions, Info (Box 19)
  - Questions (Box 19)
  - Environmental Com. (Box 19)
  - EPA (Box 19)
  - Natural Resources (Box 19)
  - Environmental (Box 19)
  - LWV File List/Clippins (Box 19)
  - Materials on PCB Cleanup (Box 19)
  - Sites: Official Documents (Box 19)
  - Solid Waste Plan and LWV Documents (Box 19)
  - Recycling (Box 20)
  - Environmental Shopping (Box 20)
  - Consent Decree (Box 20)
  - HW/PCB (Box 20)
  - LWV/NR (Box 20)
  - Fact Sheets, Committee Minutes (Box 20)
  - Natural Resources (Box 20)
  - EDF Response (Box 20)
  - NR General (Box 20)
  - Indiana Environment (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Wilderness (Box 20)
  - CIC/EPA Meeting (Box 20)
  - COPA (Box 20)
  - ABB 1995 (Box 20)
  - Natural Resources (Box 20)
  - 1995 Landfill Supplements (Box 20)
  - Natural Resources (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous Reports (6) (Box 20)
  - CIC-EPA (Box 20)
  - Health Care Reform Educational Kit (binder) (Box 21)
  - State Council, April 25-26, 2008 (Box 21)
  - State Convention, 2007 (Box 21)
  - Guide Drafts and Notes, 1998-2000 (Box 21)
  - Annual Meeting 2005, Voting Systems - Jane East (Box 21)
  - Member's Handbook, Summer 2001 (Box 21)
  - Fact Sheet - Township Trustees General Meeting (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial Convention of the LMV of Indiana, May 16-18, 2003 (Box 21)
  - LWVB-MC webpage, August 2000 (Box 21)
  - A Guide to the Public Policy Positions, 2004-2006 (Box 21)
  - The Voter, Winter 2007 (Box 21)
  - "Helping America Vote," Education Fund, June 2005 (Box 21)
  - "Next Steps on Election Reform", July 2005 (Box 21)
  - By-Laws: Policies and Practices for Review Committee, 2005 (Box 21)
  - Local Voices: Citizen Conversations on Civil Liberties and Secure Communities, 2005 (Box 21)
  - Organization Committee: Tips for Board Members, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Meth Study, 2006-2007 (Box 21)
  - "Keys to the Candidates," The Herald Times, April 26, 2007 (Box 21)
  - Utility Service Board Study, 2006-2007 (Box 21)
  - Annual Meeting, April 27, 2005 (Box 21)
  - Notes, Correspondence, Pamphlets, 2006 (Box 21)
  - "The Effects of All-Day Kindergarten" - Study, 2006 (Box 21)
  - Treasurer's Report, September 30, 2006 (Box 21)
  - League Letter, October 2006 (Box 21)
  - Meth Study, November 2006 (Box 21)
  - The Voter, Fall 2006 (Box 21)
  - Bumper Sticker, undated (Box 21)
  - League Letter, December 2006 (Box 21)
  - February 2007 General Meeting, Preparation Notes (Box 21)
  - Common Cause: "Seizing the Moment: Political Reform in America", May 31, 2006 (Box 21)
  - "Improved Medicare for All (Single Payer)", undated (Box 21)
  - Meeting Notes, 2005 (Box 21)
  - Voting Systems Fraud, 2005-2006 (Box 21)
  - Waste Management Research, 1989-1991 (Box 21)
  - Hazardous Waste Management Research, 1980-1994 (Box 22)
  - LWV Report, 1991 (Box 22)
  - Citizen Action Council (Box 22)
  - Solid Waste Management (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Election Law (Box 22)
  - Questionnaire and Summaries of Response, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Election Law A-Z (Box 22)
    (32 folders)
  - Environmental Awareness, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
  - Government (Box 23)
  - D Net (Democracy Network) (Box 23)
  - Elections - 2002 (Box 23)
  - Election 2004 (Box 23)
  - LWV Concurence: Election of the President, 2003 (Box 23)
  - Election Systems (Box 23)
  - Voter Service Booklets/Leaflets (Box 23)
  - Election Process (Box 23)
  - Voter Information, 2006 (Box 23)
  - Voter Service (Box 23)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (Box 23)
  - Making Democracy Work and Judicial (Box 23)
  - Voter Service: "Voting and Running for City Council in Alexandria" (Box 23)
  - Alliance for Better Campaigns: "The Political Standard" (Box 23)
  - NVRA (National Voter Registration Act) (Box 23)
  - Voter Service Booklets/Leaflets (Box 23)
  - Election Services (Box 23)
  - Debate Forums (Box 23)
  - Independent Judiciary (Box 23)
  - Basic Human Needs (Box 24)
  - Welfare Reform (Box 24)
  - Newsletter Items (Box 24)
  - Food Stamp Program (Box 24)
  - County Court (Box 24)
  - Poor Relief (Box 24)
  - H.R. Chairman Material (Box 24)
  - Human Resources, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Catalogs and Guides (Box 24)
  - Board Meeting Records, 1992-1995 (Box 25)
  - Board Meeting Records, 1996-1997 (Box 25)
  - Board Meeting Records, 1996-1999 (Box 25)
  - Board Meeting Records, 1999-2000 (Box 25)
  - Booklets (Box 25)
  - Civil Action (Box 25)
  - EPA- Tree 3 R's (Box 26)
  - Finances and Monthly Reports (Box 26)
  - Solid Waste Laws and Regulations (Box 26)
  - Solid Waste Bio Conversion (Box 26)
  - Solid Waste Incineration/Resource Recovery (Box 26)
  - Solid Waste (Box 26)
  - Landfill Info (Box 26)
  - HW PCB (Box 26)
  - Recycling (Box 26)
  - Indiana Board of Health, 1983 (Box 26)
  - Hazardous Waste (Box 26)
  - Recycling Brochure (Box 26)
  - LWV B-MC, Sept. 14, 1982 (Box 26)
  - Refuse Disposal Information (Box 26)
  - SW Records (Box 26)
  - Consensus Questions 1981 (Box 26)
  - SW/HW (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous (Binder) (Box 26)
  - LWV State (Box 27)
  - Incineration Legal (Box 27)
  - PCB Incineration - CIC stuff (Box 27)
  - March Units - PCBs (Box 27)
  - EPA Advisory Commission (Box 27)
  - EPA - CIC handouts (Box 27)
  - Notes from PCB meetings (Box 27)
  - Solid Waste (Box 27)
  - PCBs (Box 27)
  - Risk Assessment notes and comments (Box 27)
  - PCBs and Bloomington (Box 27)
  - EPA Superfund (Box 27)
  - SW/HW Consent Decree (Box 27)
  - SW/HW Ash Landfill (Box 27)
  - Household Hazardous Waste Collection (Box 27)
  - HHW (Box 27)
  - ToxicWatch (Box 27)
  - Hazardous Materials (Box 27)